I'm Sally the chief HR officer of
Credential Assurance Malaysia Bahad.
This award means a lot to every one of
us at Credential Assurance and I'm
extremely proud of my team.
This is an testimonial of a strong
collaboration and collective effort of
our team and the unwavering dedication
in delivering superior employee
experience in credential.
This is our first time participating in
this award and this award itself is just
not only the recognition that we
receive. It is a proof um a validation
of our purpose and especially it means a
whole deal to every one of us because
this is from our people. It comes
directly from the people whom we served
at credential. So thank you to everyone
in credential. Thank you to every
employee credential because this award
is for all of you.